http://www.honour.co.uk/privacy_policy

Menu
PVCWomen's PVCAccessoriesBasques & CorsetsBodiesBrasCatsuitsDressesGlovesKnickersLeggings & TrousersShortsSkirtsStockings and SuspendersTops & CoatsMen's PVCMen's AccessoriesMen's BottomsMen's TopsRelatedWhats NewBestsellersPlastic ClothingLycra ClothingPlus SizeVYNX - 4 Way Stretch PVC LatexWomen's LatexAccessories Basques & CorsetsBodies Bras CatsuitsDressesGlovesKnickersLeggings & TrousersShortsSkirtsStockings & SuspendersTopsBrasAccessoriesMen's LatexMen's AccessoriesMen's BottomsMen's Latex CatsuitsMen's TopsRelatedWhats NewBestsellersLatex CareLatex HoodsDatexNeoprenePlus SizeWet Look Women's Wet LookBasques & CorsetsBodiesBras & BriefsCatsuitsDressesGlovesLeggings & ShortsSkirtsStockings & SuspendersTopsMen's Wet LookMen's BottomsMen's TopsRelatedWhats NewBestsellersAccessoriesNeopreneLycra & ClubwearLeatherWomen's LeatherBasques & CorsetsBodiesBras & Briefs CatsuitsDressesGlovesSkirts & TrousersTops & JacketsMen's LeatherMen's Leather BottomsMen's Leather TopsRelatedWhats NewBestsellersAccessoriesLeatheretteBondageHoodsFetishFetish WearKinky UnderwearKinky HoodsPlastic Fetish WearRaw RubberBizarre ToysDildosButt PlugsMetal ToysBondageAll BDSM GearBlindfolds Body Restraints Chastity Cock & BallCollars & LeadsCuffsElectro SexFurnitureGagsHarnessesHead RestraintsHoodsMasksNipple ClampsPaddles & CropsSensation PlayStrap OnsWhips & FloggersSex ToysAll ToysAnal Sex ToysCondomsDildosLove Eggs & BallsLubes & OilsNipple & Clit ToysMale Sex ToysPenis RingsStrap OnsVibratorsLingerieAll Sexy LingerieBasquesBodiesBodystockingsBrasDressesGlovesHosieryKnickersLingerie SetsPasties & AccessoriesAll CorsetsOverbustUnderbustLatexLeatherPVCMen's LingerieShoes & BootsAll FootwearBootsShoesCostumesSexy CostumesMaidsMilitarySchoolNurseOtherCostume AccessoriesWigsScary CostumesMy AccountMy WishlistLoginSign Up
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Honour Privacy Policy
Introduction
At Honour we have always put the privacy and discretion of our visitors at the heart of everything we do, and we do not sell, rent or share email lists with other companies. This Privacy Policy details exactly what personal information we do collect, when we collect it and why. It also explains how we store your data and keep it safe.
Legal Basis
We rely on several different legal reasons to collect your data under GDPR these are: -
Consent
In specific situations we will collect and use your data with your specific consent. For example, if you choose to receive emails from us by subscribing to our newsletter. You have the right to remove consent at any time and where consent is our only legal basis to process your data we will stop when consent is withdrawn.
Contractual Obligations
To comply with our contractual obligations there are circumstances where we need to collect personal information. For example, if you place an order with us for delivery we will collect your address details to pass on to our courier.
Legal Compliance
We may need to collect and process your data If we are required to by law. For example, fraud prevention or other criminal activity.
Legitimate Interest
In the normal course of conducting business we may have a legitimate reason to use your data. For example, we may tailor offers to your individual preferences or use your data when acting on a customer service enquiry.
Personal Data
We may collect the follow information about you: -
·         Your name, age, date of birth and gender.
·         Contact details including home and mobile telephone numbers, billing and delivery addresses and email addresses.
·         Your interests and preferences.
·         Your on-line browsing behaviour on our sites.
·         Your purchase history.
·         Survey and feedback responses, you give us.
·         Your marketing preferences.
·         Your image if you visit any of our shops or car parks may be captured on our CCTV systems for the protection and security of our customers, staff and premises.
We mainly collect this data through your informed consent such as creating an online account with us, placing an order or signing up to our mailing list. We may also collect personal information about you through other channels such as if you were to engage with us through social media or a third-party competition.
How we use your personal data
We use your personal data to provide you with goods and services and provide you with the best possible shopping experience. Maintaining your online account, shopping history and promotional preferences are just some examples of how your data is used by us in achieving this.
Sometimes we will need to share some of this data with third parties such as our courier partners who will be delivering your order and payment gateways that process your payments to us.
We will also use your data to comply with our legal obligations in for example fraud prevention or other criminal activity.
With your consent we will use your data to provide you with relevant marketing such as emails and adverts you may see while browsing the internet.
How we protect your personal data
We take the security of our customer data very seriously and employ latest internet security features such as HTTPS and tokenised passwords to ensure its safety. We regularly carry out penetration testing and limit internal access to all data.
Klarna Payment
In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.
General information on Klarna can be found here. Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarna’s privacy policy.
Your rights
You have the following rights: -
·         Access to the personal data we hold about you.
·         To ask us to update and correct any out of date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you.
·         To opt-out of receiving all marketing communications from us
If we choose not to action your request, we will let you know why.
If you would like a copy of the data we hold on you or you would like us to update your personal information please contact the Data Protection Officer, HNR ltd, Unit 2 Finway Court, Whippendell Road. Watford. WD18 7EN or email DPO@honour.co.uk
Get a Quote for
Customer Name
Customer Email
Phone Number
Comment
Submit
Delivery
Our Stores
